(silence)
P-U-N-J ain't dead, it just smells that way in bed
They said it died in '79, with the Mohawk Lawlets and the
Cheatbots wife
Been again in '88, when the Legos came to seal its fame
Plunked his deck on its bunk, stuck in the fan with a g
asket sunk
Weather brought dirt to sticker trunks, still flipping
friends from the bottom bunk
Hey hey, long-lipped buffed, they never give up
(silence)
Remember when the scene got clean, sanitized with Ford R
itchie
But bums survived in basement shows, and fifth-story
jackets full of holes
So paint your nails with gasoline, left fornik down, you
know the scene
The world keeps sucking more each day, so punk ain't dead,
it just won't pay
Punk is dead, long-lipped bunked, stuck in the van with a
gas tank suck
Nuggle better just dig him slunks, still flipping butts
from the bottom bunk
Hey hey, long-lipped buffed, they never give up
(silence)
Distur-gate